{"data":[{"question":"What is that man ______?","a":"telling","b":"saying","c":"to say","d":"said","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something\n\n- Present continous: be + Verb_ing\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I love you ______ darling!","a":"so","b":"so many","c":"so much","d":"much","answer":"3","explain":"\n- So \/ Such in exclamations: \n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural) \n+ So + adjective ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Darling, _______ the children to go to school!","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"______ us what happened.","a":"Tell","b":"Told","c":"Say","d":"Said","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The boys didn't ______ me anything.","a":"say","b":"tell","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Negative in simple past tense: Did not + Verb infinitive ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"And this is what she _______.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Simple past tense: say- said ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ that it's going to rain today.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Say that + clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Your father ______ me that he's going to sell the car.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"3","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Simple past tense: tell- told ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What did he ______?","a":"say","b":"said","c":"tell","d":"told","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Simple past tense: say- said ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Why don't you _______ me about it?","a":"say","b":"tell","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}